logical-invest.com 2017-09-16

# Privacy Policy Smart Asset Allocation for your savings or 401k or IRA retirement

**Our Commitment To Privacy:**

Your privacy is important to us. This policy notice explains our online information usage practices to help you understand how we may use information you provide to us, how you can elect to limit the use of your information, and how we protect your privacy. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our main menu and the footer of most all pages on this site. We use the information you provide to us only to provide financial analysis services for your benefit. We do not sell or in any way release your personal information, ever.

 **The Information We Collect:**

This policy notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the Logical Invest, website. On some pages, you can subscribe to our automated investment strategy services, make requests, or ask questions. The types of personal information collected at these pages enable automated subscription payments for our automated investment strategy services, and our automated Logical Invest trade alert notifications. It also may optionally allow you to receive referral commission  payments for your earned referral credits. This information may include:

Name  
Mailing address  
Email address  
Text Phone number  
Strategy choices

On some pages, you can submit information about other people. For example, if you purchase a subscription for someone other than yourself and want it sent directly to the recipient, you will need to submit the recipient’s name and email address. In this circumstance, the types of personal information collected are:

Name of your friend  
Email address of your friend

 **Credit Card & Brokerage Account Information:**

Logical Invest is a subscription based financial advice online newsletter only. We do not require or collect any information about your actual brokerage accounts. Our subscription fees are paid to us through PayPal who holds your credit or debit card account information. We do not require or collect any information about your credit cards.

 **The Way We Use Information:**

We use the information you provide about yourself only to complete the subscription process. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete the subscription enrollment.

We use the information you provide about someone else when subscribing only to complete the subscription process and to confirm enrollment. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete the subscription process. We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties.

Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.

 **Our Use of Web Analytics:**  
We might use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website and its functionality. No information is shared with advertisers as we are an advertising-free service.  Any tracking information we collect is never tied to any individual user or email and does not include any personally identifiable information.

 **Our Use of Cookies:**  
If you subscribe to Logical Invest, you might notice our use of “cookies.”  A cookie is a small piece of alphanumeric information placed on your computer by the website you are visiting.  Once you are logged in, cookies help to maintain your security and provide a continued session identification as you move around within the site. Cookies also allow our systems to recognize your browser so we can customize your experience on our website. There are two types of cookies:

  *  **Temporary:** Cookies that are stored on your computer only during your browsing session, and are automatically deleted from your computer when you close your browser. No information is collected from your computer.
  *  **Persistent:** Cookies that are stored on your computer and are not deleted when you close your browser. Permanent cookies retain your preferences for a particular Web site, allowing those preferences to remain for future browsing sessions. No information is collected from your computer.

 **Our Commitment To Data Security:**  
To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. We share the responsibility of protecting your privacy with you. Never share your password with anyone unless you specifically wish that person or entity to have access to your private, password-protected account, and if you choose to reveal your password, you do so at your own risk. We cannot be responsible for any losses or damages you may incur.  You may update your personal information, including your user name or password, on your Account Information page at any time.

 **Our Commitment To Children’s Privacy:**  
Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 18, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 18.

 **How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information:**  
You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect and maintain by clicking **“My Account”** from the main menu and selecting the sub-category of interest to you. To protect your privacy and security, we will require username and password log in to verify your identity before granting access.

 **How To Contact Us:**  
Should you have questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please contact us by one of the methods provided at Contact Us.
